♪ ♪
Hurry up. Smithsonian's
sick! Come on!
He looked fine two
hours ago, Tommy.
Well, he's sick.
He didn't want his sugar.
There, see?
He looks fine to me.
I'll show you.
Be careful now.
He pasted me a
good one last week.
He won't hurt me.
He's my friend.
See? He won't take
his sugar. He's sick.
I'll be damned.
What the hell's going on here?
Smithsonian's coming
down with something.
So call the vet.
Why aren't those
stalls cleared out?
He was concerned
about the horse.
I've got a ton of hay coming in,
no place to put it.
Now get to work.
Yes, sir, Mr. Clint.
If I were you, I'd
spend a little less time
sticking up for him and a
little more time doing your job.
Hyah! Come on! Hyah! Get it!
Move!
Yah!
Move it! Move!
Mrs. Taylor, that
horse is all lathered up.
He tried to throw me.
I'm teaching him a lesson.
Tell her she can't
ride Henry J like that!
Tell the boss's wife she can't?
I don't think so, Tommy.
Hyah!
She's hurting him!
Stop! Stop!
Let go of me!
Are you sure you're okay?
What the hell kind
of stunt was that?!
I could have broken my neck!
Your neck's not hurt.
You idiot.
You were hurting Henry J.
Get this moron out of my sight
and keep him there!
Tommy, let's go.
Now! Come on, Tommy.
Let's go. Get out of here.
I'm telling my
husband about this.
So am I.
Dad wants to sell this horse.
He'll be mad as hell
when he hears you've
ridden him into the ground.
Nobody's gonna buy a
horse that isn't schooled.
Nobody's gonna buy
one that's foundered.
You walk that horse
till he's bone-dry.
She's the boss.
Sandra's a witch. You walk him.
Oh, and I wouldn't go sucking up
to her today, if I were you.
She might smell
what's on your breath.
Come in.
Mr. Clint said you
want to see me?
Tommy, how did you
know Smithsonian was sick?
Oh, 'cause I knew.
Dr. Simpkin says
that he can't even play
with his friends no more.
Well, just for a while.
And that's because we don't
want them to get sick, too.
And because you
were so observant,
Dr. Simpkin doesn't
think they will.
I don't know how you do it,
but once again,
you just saved us
a lot of money in vet bills.
Thank you.
Oh...
Oh, no!
It's, it's all right.
No! No!
No! It's all right. No big deal.
But it was so
pretty, and I broke it.
A little glue and it'll
be as good as new.
I have glue.
I'll fix it, okay?
Okay.
I'll fix it real good, Sandra.
Hello.
Sandra, it's Patricia.
I fell off Henry J. And
I was mad at myself.
And embarrassed.
But I-I shouldn't have
taken it out on the horse.
Or you.
It's all right.
No, it isn't.
Um... let me
apologize in person.
Come to dinner tonight.
Oh, I'd like to, really, um,
but I'm gonna be working late.
Something urgent's come up.
In fact, I need to talk to Dad.
Oh... He's, he's taking a nap.
You want me to wake him?
No, it'll wait.
May I have a rain
check on dinner?
Sure.
Anytime.
Bye.
What are you doing?
Fixing Sandra's horse.
What happened to it?
Aw... I broke it when
she was kissing me.
The rest of us can't
hardly say boo to her,
and you got her kissing you.
Sandra and me are friends.
You ought to be; you
practically grew up together.
Did you finish
stacking that hay?
I forgot.
Mr. Clint's gonna be mad.
Not if you go back out
there and finish it up.
It's okay.
It takes a while
for that glue to dry.
Okay.
Sandra? Fixed your horse.
Hey, Tommy.
Tommy?
What's wrong?
Nothing there.
He's in here!
Don't hurt him.
Stay back.
You come along now.
Don't give us any trouble.
Come on. Stand up, son.
Come on.
Easy now.
Put the cuffs on him.
Take it easy, son.
Let me go, please! Stop it!
Tommy! Let me go!
Let me go! Let me go!
No!
Tommy, stop it!
Now stop fighting right now.
Now Tommy, you do what the
policemen tell you to do, hear?
Yes, sir.
Put your hands behind your back.
Hello, Sam.
Ben.
I, um, I read the paper.
I'm really sorry about Sandra.
Thanks.
Things sure are never
gonna be the same
around here without her.
Well, it's... it's been a
while. How you been?
Oh, fine, fine.
The years have generally
treated me pretty good.
Uh, Sam, uh...
is there anything
I can do for you?
There's nothing, really, Ben.
Well, yeah, yeah.
The police have
arrested Tommy Jenks.
Yeah, I read about that.
Tommy's retarded.
His father was one
of my best friends,
and his mother
ran away from home
when Tommy was
just five years old,
and then his father died
a few years after that.
I raised him
alongside of Sandra.
He's a good boy.
Ben, he doesn't lie, and
he said he didn't do it.
Oh, honey, I've been
looking all over for you.
You should be up
at the house resting.
I can't.
I just lay there thinking.
Oh, Ben, this is
my wife, Patricia.
Patricia, Ben Matlock,
a very old friend.
Hello. Hello.
Honey, please.
Tommy Jenks
wouldn't kill anybody.
Bad enough losing Sandra, but...
having Tommy accused of it...
Can you help, Ben?
It would, it would
mean the world to me.
I knew Miss Sandra was dead,
'cause sometimes, on the farm,
horses, they get dead.
They get all cold,
and they don't move,
and that's just the way she was,
and it made me scared to
see Miss Sandra like that.
Come sit down.
That's why you ran away and hid?
Can I go home now?
No.
Not, not yet.
Oh.
I forgot to feed the horses
their oats this morning.
Mr. Clint's gonna be so mad.
Oh, I, oh, I'm sure
Mr. Clint got somebody
else to do that.
I hope so.
I hope, I hope he did.
Tommy, listen.
Tommy, listen to me.
Are... Are you listening?
Yeah.
Okay.
Now, this may be hard
for you to understand,
but you have to try, okay?
Okay.
Some people think
you killed Sandra,
and that means there's
going to have to be a trial.
Are you with me?
Do you understand?
I didn't, I didn't clean
out the stalls either.
Tommy, Tommy,
listen to me, listen to me.
We can tell the judge...
He's the man in
charge of the trial...
that you wish to plead
diminished capacity.
That means that
maybe you killed Sandra,
but you didn't know
what you were doing
and you didn't mean to.
That's wrong!
I didn't kill Sandra.
But, Tommy, see, sometimes,
- sometimes we have...
- Oh, Lord.
Tommy... sometimes
we have to make a deal.
We tell the judge you did it,
and in return,
he sends you to a
hospital for awhile
instead of to prison.
I don't, I don't want
to go to a hospital.
I don't want to go to a prison.
I want to go home.
Tommy... I want to go home.
Did you kill Sandra?
Tommy would never hurt Sandra.
Then that's what we'll have
to prove to a judge and jury.
Okay?
Okay.
Can I go home now?
Tommy... I'm gonna try.
Your Honor, the State feels
a complete psychiatric
examination of the defendant
is necessary in order to
determine whether he is
competent to stand trial.
We have reason to believe
Mr. Jenks lacks
sufficient capacity
to know, understand
and appreciate
the charges against him.
However, I'm sure
defense counsel
and I can agree...
Uh, uh, Y-Your Honor...
Uh, excuse me for
interrupting, Ms. March,
but I believe I can
save us all a lot of time.
Uh, a complete psychiatric
exam and evaluation,
uh, on my client, has
just been completed
by Dr. Samuel Chadwick.
Uh, I believe you
know Dr. Chadwick.
He's provided you with expert
testimony on several occasions.
Yes, I know Dr. Chadwick...
Well, as it happens,
Dr. Chadwick
knows my client, too.
Has for many years.
And after reacquainting himself
with my client,
uh, in an interview,
he prepared this evaluation.
In it, he concludes that
"Tommy Jenks is
a benign individual
"who possesses great
respect for authority figures,
"is emotionally
attached to his home
"out at the Taylor
thoroughbred farm,
and that he is unequivocally
competent to stand trial."
Do you know what you're doing?
You just blew the opportunity
to plead diminished capacity
and/or insanity.
I know.
I see no reason why the court
shouldn't accept
this evaluation.
Ms. March?
I... I suppose I see
no objection either.
Oh, good.
Your Honor, uh, defense
waives reading of the charges,
pleads innocent and
wishes to proceed
directly to the matter of bail.
Ms. March, any recommendations?
Yes.
Yes, Your Honor.
Um, in view of the
fact that the defendant
stands accused
of a capital crime
and has tried to escape
justice by resisting arrest,
the State asks that bail be
set at one hun... $250,000.
Uh, Your Honor...
I'd like to remind
the prosecutor
that she has agreed with
Dr. Chadwick's conclusion
that Tommy Jenks is
a harmless individual,
does what he's told
and has strong ties
to his community.
Bail is $25,000.
Trial is set for April 16.
Can I go home now?
Yeah.
Come on, Tommy.
I'm going home.
Well, Sam said he'd be
up this road, just
past the house.
Want me to drive you?
No, that's okay.
The walk will do me good.
Sam, when you take a walk,
you just go ahead and
take one, don't you?
Two miles out, two miles back.
That's supposed to keep me
from getting another heart attack.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
What's, uh, what's in there?
It's a grave.
Best horse I ever
had's buried there.
Knight's Legend.
You remember?
Oh, that's right.
He won the Triple Crown.
Yeah.
Broke his leg winning
the Peach Tree Stakes
about four years ago.
I had to put him down.
I had my heart attack
just a few days after that.
Couldn't you have
patched him up?
Well, maybe; maybe not.
But he was in such pain...
Sandra said I was wrong.
She said I...
that I lost a ton of
money in stud fees.
But I just couldn't
see him going like that.
Sandra always did say
I was no businessman.
That...
that's why she took
over running the farm.
Thank God she did.
I was borrowing
money right and left.
How she kept us out of
bankruptcy, I'll never know.
Uh, how long, how long
you been married to Patricia?
Oh, about two years.
Things were starting
to pick up then.
Uh-huh.
I guess, uh,
Sandra and Patricia got
along pretty well, didn't they?
Patricia was only five
years older than Sandra.
That didn't make
it easy for Sandra.
And Sandra insisted that Pat
sign a prenuptial agreement.
Oh, well...
That didn't make
it easy for Pat.
That's good though.
You know...
women are a lot more
complicated than horses.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
Okay.
Oh, she's a beauty.
Hi again.
Michelle Thomas.
We met at Tommy's hearing.
Right. Hello.
Hi.
Brood mare. Just bought her.
Actually, practically stole her.
Come on.
Turn her loose in the
paddock for a walk.
Yes, ma'am.
Well, it looks like
you've pretty much
taken charge of
things around here.
Somebody had to.
Since Sam's heart attack,
he can't do too much.
Uh, if you'll excuse me,
I'd like to go clean up.
Um, were you home the
night Sandra was murdered?
Yes.
Did you see or hear
anything out of the ordinary?
Nope.
What about your husband?
Actually, Sam went into town
for about an hour after dinner.
And, uh, when he came
back, that's when I told him
Sandra had mentioned that
she wanted to talk to him.
That's when he found the body.
Well, what made you think
she'd still be in her office?
She told me she'd
be working late.
When I called to apologize for
something that happened earlier.
Oh, you had an argument?
Ms. Thomas, make up your mind
whether you and Mr. Matlock
are defending Tommy
or prosecuting me.
Excuse me.
Donovan, haul a bale of hay
out to the paddock and break it up.
New mare's out there.
I'll do it, Mr. Clint!
I said Donovan.
After all, you're not gonna
be around here much longer.
Well, I'm not going anyplace.
Hell, you're going to prison.
Cut it out, Clint.
It's a scary place, kid.
Well, Mr. Matlock, he
said I was gonna stay here.
He lied.
They're gonna put you away, boy.
No!
What the hell'd you do that for?
Well... I'll bet you
didn't have to do
much of that when
you were foreman.
Ben Matlock.
Yes, sir.
Must have been quite
a shock when she...
chose Clint and
demoted you that way.
Didn't make me real happy.
Must not have made you too mad.
You're still here.
I'm ten years
past starting over.
Sandra knew that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um, anything else you
want to know, Mr. Matlock?
Well, yeah.
You got any idea
who killed Sandra?
No.
You think it was Tommy?
I can't believe it was Tommy.
It wasn't me.
I was in the bunkhouse reading
right up till the time
the police came.
Uh, you couldn't have maybe gone
you know, somewhere...?
What the Sam Hill?!
Somebody's starting my truck!
That's Tommy!
Tommy! Tommy, come back here!
What the hell got into him?
♪ ♪
Here you go.
Ice machine's behind the office
next to the pop machine.
And don't go
smacking the TV around
thinking it's broken,
'cause it ain't.
Cable's out, so it only
gets two channels.
That'll be 18 bucks.
Need anything else,
just give me a holler
We don't have the
money to do that right now
and you know it! The
business isn't going that well!
I'm not talking about money!
I'm talking about
what you promised!
I don't even
remember! You're crazy!
I can't... What am
I...? I can't trust you!
Give me that
briefcase! Gimme it!
No, no!
Give it here! What's in here?!
I'll punch ya!
Ah...
Congratulations, Sydney, I hear
you're kicking the banana habit.
Oh, I am, Stanley, I am, I am!
As soon as my
emergency supply is gone.
Oh, I feel so
refreshed. So refreshed.
Hi, Sidney.
Ah! For heaven's sakes,
Cleo, you startled me.
I'm gonna call the manager
if you don't turn that TV down!
I'm sorry, Sidney. We
just want you to know
that we're proud of
what you're doing.
And we're going to help
you fight the banana habit.
Who needs help? Who needs it?
You will, Sydney,
when the wind comes
from the banana plantation.
I'll punch you!
Oh, no, the wind has
shifted toward the jungle!
That crazy elephant...
Uh, hey, Mr. Donovan.
You got a minute? I want
to ask you something.
Mr. Purdy... What do you want?
Did you run Tommy off on purpose
or was it just
regular stupidity?
I figured it was time
somebody leveled with him.
That was a jackass thing to do
and you know it.
Where were you when
Sandra Taylor was killed?
I don't remember.
Me and Sandra
got along just fine,
and that's all I got to say.
Hmm.
And the farmer eats it.
Great pig like that, you
don't eat 'em all at once.
Hey...
Hey, you play one mean
game of video there, boy.
Thank you.
It's real easy.
You just shoot these
little guys with this.
Lyle, Lyle, now,
did you hear that?
Why, I bet we... I bet we got us
a college graduate
here or something.
Yeah, maybe a rocket scientist.
You a rocket
scientist, boy, hmm?
Oh, hey, where you going?
You guys are teasing me.
No, we're not.
Yes, you are.
Oh, did you hear that, Jed? Huh?
I think he just
called me a liar.
Now... now, you
gotta understand...
Lyle here's my friend.
And I don't like it when
people call him a liar.
I don't like it at all.
Whoa! You captured him!
Good work, gentlemen.
Now speak very softly
and watch what you say.
And who are you?
I am Dr. Tyler Hudson,
criminal psychiatrist.
And you gentlemen have just
captured a very dangerous man.
Come on.
This half-wit?
Hey, watch what you say
or you may set him off again.
What do you mean, set him off?
Let's put it this way:
there were three
of us escorting him
to a violent ward.
Somebody said the wrong
thing. I'm the only one still walking.
Tommy, Mr. Matlock
sent me for you.
Come with me, okay?
Is he mad?
Naw, he's not mad.
He knows you didn't mean
to break Dr. Scribner's neck.
Come on.
Okay.
1-65-83-24. You got it, Ben.
Thank you.
Well, Sandra's
leather briefcase.
Here's a telephone book.
Okay... Maybe we'll
find something in here.
These are old calendars.
Huh, that's odd.
Well, maybe she was
cleaning out her files.
Why would she put
these old calendars,
all this wrinkled
stuff in her briefcase?
Huh, that is weird.
Oh... What is it?
That's a picture
of Knight's Legend.
That's a... a
championship racehorse.
Sam told me all about it.
Well, Sam said
I'd find you here.
You look surprised, Mr. Matlock.
When I first married
Sam, everybody thought
I was a fluffy-headed bimbo
after an older man's money.
They hated me for it.
Yeah.
Now they take me for a smart,
tough-minded woman
capable of running this farm
and hate me for
it... except Sam.
As long as Sam loves me,
who cares what
anyone else thinks?
Hmm.
Do you recognize this horse?
Three white stockings
and a sorrel foot.
Looks light old pictures
I've seen of Knight's Legend.
Valuable horse.
That's what I've heard.
Uh, Mr. Purdy, how long
have you been foreman
out at the Taylor
Thoroughbred Horse Farm?
Three, three-and-half years.
Uh-huh. And where did
you work before then?
The Double Daisy
Farm, up in Tennessee.
How many years?
Two or three.
Mm-hmm. And where'd
you work before that?
Well, I don't know. I've
worked many places.
Yeah... Yeah, you have.
In fact, you've held down
more jobs in the past ten years
than most people do in
a lifetime, haven't you?
Objection: relevancy.
It calls for speculation.
Sustained.
Yes, why, why did you
move around so much?
It was just the way things were.
Uh-huh. Mr. Purdy, uh,
you like to do a little drinking
while you're working, don't ya?
Not anymore. I'm
clean and sober.
Well, now, Patricia Taylor
and John Donovan work
with you every day.
I don't expect they would agree
that you've quit
drinking, do you? Well, I...
I'm sure that Sandra either
knew it or suspected it.
You had an argument
with her about it,
didn't you? I did not.
Who are these,
these fellas here, um...
Norman Stroud, Eugene
Buford, Tex Rafferty?
They're all foremen.
Top-of-the-line foremen.
Yes. And you knew
that Sandra had
called all of them
and offered your job to them.
No, I did not.
She was gonna fire you.
It was just a matter of time.
And you dared not lose this job
because if you lose
this job, chances are
you'd never get another one.
She wasn't gonna fire me.
You went to her, you pled with
her to give you one more chance.
And when she refused,
you took Tommy's knife
put on your old work clothes...
No. And you killed her.
And who better to frame
than this poor innocent boy.
But you continued to provoke him
till he ran away and made
himself look even more guilty
No!
When she told me
she was gonna fire me,
I was plenty mad all right.
I went down to the
Continental Bar that night
and I started drinking.
And I didn't quit drinking till I
passed out in the middle of the floor.
Ask the bartender.
Ask all the people who had to
step over my carcass all night.
I started drinking
again, it's true.
But I didn't kill Sandra.
No further questions.
Ms. March, redirect?
No, Your Honor.
This court is in recess
until 10:00 Monday morning.
Is it over now?
Not yet.
Are you sure?
You sure it's not a coincidence?
Huh.
Okay. Well, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Let's go. Where we going?
Out to the Taylor farm.
Does Tyler have something
special going on this weekend?
Not that I know of.
Good. I got something
I want him to do.
Hey, Tyler, you
finding anything?
Hell, no!
Keep digging!
Mr. Taylor, you've
raised thoroughbreds
for 45 years.
Now, how do you make
money in your business?
You raise horses
that, uh, win all the time
and make you a lot
of money at the track?
Well, I want the
horses that we raise
to bring home as many
purses as they can, yes.
But I also want the
horses to make me money
after their racing
career's over.
You're talking about stud fees.
Yes, sir.
The real object of the game
is to raise a champion
for whose offspring,
other breeders will
pay handsomely.
Would you tell the court
who, uh, Knight's Legend was.
Ah... that's the best
horse I ever raised.
True champion, inside and out.
Won every race he ever entered
and would have been
worth millions in stud fees.
What happened?
I got greedy.
He was a proven commodity.
There was absolutely no reason
for that horse
ever to race again.
Except that I knew he'd win,
and I wanted the money.
So I entered him in
a big handicap race.
And he shattered a foreleg
about 20 yards
from the finish line.
We took him home, but,
uh, it didn't do any good.
I just had to have
him destroyed.
Who put him down? You?
No, no.
I had my foreman do it.
I-I couldn't even bear to watch.
Your foreman, uh, Clint Purdy?
Oh, no.
Mr. John Donovan was
my foreman at the time.
He took a .38 pistol and
a shovel out into the field,
and he didn't come back
until after he buried him.
Well, thank you very much.
And no further questions.
Your witness.
No questions, Your Honor.
Witness may step down.
Call John Donovan to the stand.
Now, Mr. Donovan,
how long have you worked
out at the Taylor ranch?
Close to 25 years.
And, uh,
you and Mr. Taylor were
very good, very old friends,
weren't you?
Still are.
Uh, at-at-at one point,
he talked with you about,
uh, making you a partner,
didn't he?
We discussed it, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
But, uh, but that didn't,
uh, that didn't work out.
No.
And, uh, up until, oh,
three and a half years ago,
you were foreman, but then,
that was taken away from you.
When Sandra took over the
farm, she did some reorganizing,
gave my job to Clint Purdy.
Which was fine with me.
It's a young man's job, anyway.
You ever get the feeling
you're being shoved aside?
No.
Oh. Uh, have you ever,
have you ever seen this picture?
No.
You know who this horse is?
Don't you think he looks a
little bit like Knight's Legend?
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah.
I do. I do.
I, um... I had that
picture blown up.
Look at that. Look at that.
That nice?
I had it blown up.
And, uh, look here.
See, right under the tote board,
says, "J-E-F-F"
and looks like an "E."
So I took a chance and
called Jefferson Downs.
That's a little track
outside of Tallahassee.
You ever been over there?
Many times. Yeah.
And I was just curious when
this race might have been run.
And so I asked
them if they could tell
by the odds up over
the tote board there
when it was run and
if they had a record.
And you know, they did.
They had a record
of it in their computer.
And this race was run
March 19 of this year...
Three months ago.
Guess it can't be a picture
of Knight's Legend then, can it?
No, no.
No.
It could be a picture
of Knight's Legend's
colt though, couldn't it?
Well, that's impossible.
You heard Mr. Taylor.
Knight's Legend was destroyed
before he could be
used for breeding.
He was supposed to be.
But was he, Mr. Donovan?
Yes. I buried him myself.
Where?
The edge of the south
pasture, where it's fenced off.
That whole area was
dug up this weekend.
There's nothing buried there.
You never put him down, did you?
Yes, I did.
You felt you had
nothing to lose.
You were losing everything
at the farm anyway.
And you know,
if it had turned
out differently,
everybody would've
been so grateful.
You hauled that horse off.
And with the tricks
and knowledge
you've learned over the years,
you nursed him back to health,
didn't you?
No, you don't know
what you're saying.
That's impossible.
You don't call him
Knight's Legend, no.
And you had to
forge a lot of papers,
and you had to do
something about the tattoo
that all thoroughbreds
have under their upper lip.
But that horse
is alive and well.
Isn't he?
I'm telling you,
that's impossible.
Mr. Donovan, you
should never have thrown
your credit card receipts on
the floorboard of your truck.
Too easy for my
man Tyler to find.
I know why you've been
buying so much gasoline
over at Piedmont, Alabama.
Because you've
been boarding a horse
at a little stable
outside of town.
That horse.
That's Knight's Legend.
This court will come to order!
Your Honor, I object!
Order!
Order in the court!
Now, please be seated.
Mr. Matlock, how
long do you intend
to have this animal
in my courtroom?
Your Honor, this
is not a Bengal tiger
or a python snake.
This is just a brown
horse who likes people.
See?
Nice horsey.
A few moments, Your Honor.
I'll hold you to that.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Donovan, perhaps you'd
like to change your testimony.
That is Knight's
Legend, isn't it?
Yes.
It must have taken
every penny you had
to board that
horse all this time.
That's why you're still
working at the ranch.
You couldn't make
much on stud fees,
because you had to keep
his existence a secret.
All you could do is wait
for an offspring to
race and hopefully win.
And this is a photograph
of Knight's Legend's
offspring, isn't it?
Yes.
You know where
I got this picture?
From Sandra Taylor's briefcase.
I don't know where she
got it... Doesn't matter.
But I am sure the instant
she saw this photograph,
she saw the resemblance
to Knight's Legend.
She showed it
to you, didn't she?
Why would she do that?
I don't know.
Maybe to see what you thought.
But... when she
showed it to you,
you knew it was
only a matter of time
before she put it all together.
And then, it would
truly all be over.
So that night,
when Tommy left the bunkhouse,
you put on your work
gloves, took Tommy's knife,
went up to Sandra's
office and killed her.
And then you started
looking for this picture.
You looked in her briefcase,
throwing stuff here and
there out of her briefcase.
In the wastebasket,
throwing stuff in and
out of the briefcase.
Tommy's coming all the time!
And you finally, you put
stuff back in the briefcase.
New stuff, old stuff,
papers out of the trash can.
You never found the picture
because Tommy was coming.
Tommy was coming.
And you wanted
Tommy... to take the blame,
didn't you?
Isn't he pretty?
Hey.
Did he bite you?
No.
He remembered me.
www.tvsubtitles.net